19th and 20th century Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Russia (Box 82)
  - Cities (Box 83)
    - Moscow (Box 84)
      - Government Buildings (Box 84)
        - Palace of the Soviets (Box 84)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 85)
      - Libraries (Box 85)
      - Monuments (Box 85)
        - Tomb of Lenin (Box 85)
      - Museums (Box 85)
      - Office Buildings (Box 85)
      - Palaces (Box 85)
        Xx Government Buildings
      - Stations (Box 85)
      - Schools (Box 85)
      - Squares (Box 85)
      - Theaters (Box 85)
    - Mount Elbnes (Box 85)
    - Nikolaev (Box 85)
    - Nishini-Novgorod (Box 85)
    - Nowosbirsk (Box 85)
    - Odessa (Box 85)
    - Ouglitch (Box 85)
    - Petrovorest (Box 85)
    - Rostov (Box 85)
    - Stanligrad (Box 85)
    - Tambov (Box 85)
    - Tsarkoe Selo (Box 85)
    - Uglich (Box 85)
    - Velikaya Gyba (Box 85)
    - Viazna (Box 85)
    - Vilna (Box 85)
    - Zaporozhe (Box 85)
- Spain (Box 86)
  - Various (Box 86)
  - Cities (Box 86)
    - Barcelona (Box 86)
      - Churches (Box 86)
        - Church of the Colonia Guell (Box 86)
        - Sagrada Familia (Holy Family) (Box 86)
      - Estates (Box 86)
        - Finca Miralles (Box 86)
      - Exhibitions (Box 86)
        - International Exhibitiion, 1929 (Box 86)
        - German Pavilion, 1929 (Box 86)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 86)
        - Casa Batllo (Box 86)
        - Casa Calvet (Box 86)
        - Casa Guell (Box 86)
        - Casa Mila (Box 87)
          - Rooftop (Box 87)
        - Casa Vicens (Box 87)
      - Parks (Box 87)
        - Parque Guell (Box 87)
      - Theaters (Box 87)
        - Palacio de la Musica Catalana (Box 87)
    - Cordova (Box 87)
    - Garraf (Box 87)
    - La Carolina (Box 87)
    - Lerma (Box 87)
    - Madrid (Box 87)
    - Navarra (Box 87)
    - Nuevo Baztan (Box 87)
    - Puente la Reina Navarra (Box 87)
    - Segovia (Box 87)
    - Toledo (Box 87)
- Sweden (Box 87)
  [Boxes 87-90]
  - General Architects (Box 87)
    - Hellden, David (Box 87)
    - Markelius, Sven (Box 87)
  - General Interiors (Box 87)
  - Cities (Box 87)
    - Falun (Box 87)
    - Goteborg (Box 87)
      - Various (Box 87)
      - Church (Box 87)
    - Halsingborg (Box 87)
    - Kevinge (Box 88)
    - Kvarnholmen (Box 88)
    - Linkoping (Box 88)
    - Lund (Box 88)
    - Malmo (Box 88)
      - Crematories (Box 88)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 88)
      - Museums (Box 88)
      - Recreation (Box 88)
        - Entertainment Center (Box 88)
      - Theaters (Box 88)
    - Orebro (Box 88)
    - Skodeborg (Box 88)
    - Stockholm (Box 88)
      - Planning (Box 88)
      - Banks (Box 88)
      - Crematories (Box 88)
      - Churches (Box 88)
        - Engelbrecht (Box 88)
        - Hogalids (Box 88)
      - Clubs (Box 88)
        - S.A.R. Builders Club (Box 88)
        - Students Club (Box 88)
      - Community Center (Box 88)
      - Exhibitions (Box 88)
        - 1930 (Box 88)
      - Government Buildings (Box 88)
        - Court House (Box 88)
        - Parliament House (Box 88)
        - Town Hall (Box 89)
      - Hospitals (Box 89)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 89)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 89)
      - Housing (Box 89)
      - Libraries (Box 89)
      - Museums (Box 89)
      - Recreation (Box 89)
      - Restaurants (Box 89)
      - Schools (Box 90)
        - Elementary Schools (Box 90)
        - Torsviks School (Box 90)
        - University of Engineering & Architecture (Box 90)
      - Squares (Box 90)
      - Theaters (Box 90)
- Switzerland (Box 90)
  - Architects (Box 90)
    - Nitzschke, Oscar (Box 90)
  - Cities (Box 90)
    - Adelboden (Box 90)
    - Basel (Box 90)
      - Churches (Box 90)
        - Christian Science Church (Box 90)
        - S. Antoine Church (Box 90)
        - S. Antoine Church (Box 90)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 90)
        - Hoffmann La Roche Factory (Box 90)
      - Museums (Box 90)
      - Stores (Box 90)
    - Bellach (Box 91)
    - Bellinzona (Box 91)
    - Berne (Box 91)
    - Benningen (Box 91)
    - Dornach (Box 91)
    - Geneva (Box 91)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 91)
      - League of Nations (Box 91)
    - La Chaux-de-Fonds (Box 91)
    - Lattau (Box 91)
    - Lake Geneva (Box 91)
    - Le Locle (Box 91)
    - Lucerne (Box 91)
      - Churches (Box 91)
        - S. Karl Church (Box 91)
      - Museums (Box 91)
        - Museum & Auditorium (Box 91)
      - Schools (Box 92)
    - Oberuzwill (Box 92)
    - Oberuzwill (Box 92)
    - Valsainte (Box 92)
    - Vevey (Box 92)
    - Zermatt (Box 92)
    - Zurich (Box 92)
      - Churches (Box 92)
        - Christian Science Church (Box 92)
        - S. Paul Church (Box 92)
        - Wollishofen Protestant Church (Box 92)
      - Exhibition (Box 92)
        - Swiss National Exposition, 1939 (Box 92)
      - Hospitals (Box 92)
      - Housing (Box 92)
        - Bellaria Park Houses (Box 92)
        - Doldertal Apartments (Box 92)
        - Neubhl Apartments (Box 92)
      - Recreation (Box 92)
        - Allenmoos Bath (Box 92)
      - Schools (Box 92)
        - Kindergarteen (Box 92)
        - Plytechnic Institute (Box 92)
        - Technical High School (Box 92)
      - Theaters (Box 92)
    - Zurich-Altstetten (Box 92)
      - Churches (Box 92)
        - Reformed Church (Box 92)
    - Zurich-Oerlikou (Box 93)
- Syria (Box 93)
  - Damascus (Box 93)
- Turkey (Box 93)
  - Various (Box 93)
- Yugoslavia (Box 93)
  - Dubrovnil (Ragusa) (Box 93)
  - Zagreb (Box 93)
- Latin America (Box 93)
  - Argentina (Box 93)
    - Architects (Box 93)
      - Williams, Amancio (Box 93)
    - Cities (Box 93)
      - Buenos Aires (Box 93)
        - Banks (Box 93)
        - Hospitals (Box 93)
  - Bolivia (Box 93)
    - Cochabamba (Box 93)
    - Potosi (Box 93)
    - Sucre (Box 93)
  - Brazil (Box 93)
    - Architects (Box 93)
      - Burle, Marx Roberto (Box 93)
      - Niemeyer, Oscar (Box 93)
      - Roberts, M & M. (Box 93)
    - Cities (Box 93)
      - Belo Horizonte (Box 93)
      - Manaos (Box 93)
      - Brasilia (Box 93)
        - Plans (Box 93)
        - General views (Box 93)
        - Banks (Box 93)
        - Churches (Box 93)
          - Cathedral (Box 93)
        - Government Buildings (Box 94)
          - Judiciary Building (Box 94)
          - Ministry Buildings (Box 94)
          - Triangle of the Powers (Box 94)
        - Hotels (Box 94)
        - Housing (Box 94)
          - Residential Superblocks (Box 94)
        - Palaces (Box 94)
          - Palace of Alvorada (Box 94)
      - Olinda (Box 94)
      - Ouro Preto (Box 94)
      - Pampulha (Box 94)
        - Restaurant (Box 94)
      - Petropolis (Box 94)
      - Rio de Janeiro (Box 94)
        - Airports (Box 94)
        - Banks (Box 94)
        - Clubs (Box 94)
        - Government Buildings (Box 94)
          - British Embassy (Box 94)
          - Ministry of Ed. & Health (Box 94)
        - Hospitals (Box 94)
        - Hotels (Box 94)
        - Housing-Apartments (Box 94)
        - Houses-Residences (Box 95)
        - Office Buildings (Box 95)
          - Brasilian Press Association (Box 95)
          - Industrial Institute (Box 95)
        - Schools (Box 95)
          - Day Nursery (Box 95)
      - Salvador (Box 95)
      - Sao Paolo (Box 95)
  - Chile (Box 95)
    - Puerto Montt (Box 95)
    - Santiago (Box 95)
  - Colombia (Box 95)
    - Bogota (Box 95)
    - Cartagena (Box 95)
  - Ecuador (Box 95)
  - Guatemala (Box 95)
  - Mexico (Box 95)
    - Architects (Box 95)
      - Ward, H.G. (Box 95)
    - Cities (Box 95)
      - Mexico City (Box 95)
        - Government Buildings (Box 95)
          - Federal District Building (Box 95)
        - Monuments (Box 95)
        - Museums (Box 95)
        - Schools (Box 95)
        - Theaters (Box 96)
          - Palace of Fine Arts (Box 96)
      - Monterrey (Box 96)
      - Queretaro (Box 96)
      - San Jose del Altillo (Box 96)
      - Taxco (Box 96)
  - Peru (Box 96)
  - Venezuela (Box 96)
    - Amuay Bay (Box 96)
    - Caracas (Box 96)
    - Coro (Box 96)
- Caribbean (Box 96)
  - Various (Box 96)
  - Barbados (Box 96)
    - Various (Box 96)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 96)
    - Higuey (Box 96)